galveston.com 2005-04-03

# PRIVACY POLICY

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Your privacy on the Internet is important to us. As part of the operation of GALVESTON.COM, GALVESTONCVB.COM, GALVESTONTOURISM.COM, GALVESTONPARKBOARD.ORG, GALVESTONONLINE.COM, GALVESTONTEXAS.US, GALVESTONTX.US, VISITGALVESTONTEXAS.COM and ESCAPEANDEXPLORE.COM (henceforth, referred to as "OUR WEBSITE(S)"), we gather certain types of information about OUR WEBSITE(S) users, and we would like to explain the types of information we gather, what we do with it and how to correct or change the information. 

OUR WEBSITE(S) collect two types of personally identifying information from users: personal data (such as names and e-mail addresses); and aggregated data (such as information about traffic patterns on OUR WEBSITE(S) on a daily basis). 

**Personal Data** Personal data is collected when users provide personal data to OUR WEBSITE(S), for example in registering for electronic newsletters or other membership services, in answering surveys, in requesting information, and purchasing items from OUR WEBSITE(S). Also, we collect the e-mail addresses of users who post messages to our message boards (forum). **Aggregated Information** Aggregated information, such as which pages users access or visit and information volunteered by users, such as survey information and/or site registrations, is collected through various methods. For example, OUR WEBSITE(S) collect IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers, the computers that "serve up" Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address, and when you request a page from OUR WEBSITE(S) do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, so although your session will be logged, you will remain anonymous to us. OUR WEBSITE(S) collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to provide aggregate data to advertisers about the volume of use on OUR WEBSITE(S). **Use of Cookies** OUR WEBSITE(S) also use "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that most major Web sites write to your hard drive for record keeping purposes when you visit them. Cookies allow OUR WEBSITE(S) to measure activity on the Site and to improve your user experience, for example, by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences, thus allowing you to visit various member-only parts of the Site without reregistering. Cookies are used by OUR WEBSITE(S) to measure activity on the Site and make improvements and updates based on which areas are popular and which are not. OUR WEBSITE(S) do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. Except for personal information voluntarily provided by you (i.e., during membership registration or a request for information), OUR WEBSITE(S) do not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, nor is that information shared with any third parties whatsoever. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers, which is standard in the Internet industry. OUR WEBSITE(S) do not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to OUR WEBSITE(S) privacy policies.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of the Site will not function properly if you do so. 

**Use of Information Collected by GALVESTON.COM, GALVESTONCVB.COM, GALVESTONTOURISM.COM, GALVESTONPARKBOARD.ORG, GALVESTONONLINE.COM, GALVESTONTEXAS.US, GALVESTONTX.US, VISITGALVESTONTEXAS.COM and ESCAPEANDEXPLORE.COM** OUR WEBSITE(S) use both the personal and aggregated information we collect for multiple purposes. The information is used to improve the content of the Site, to customize the content and/or layout of the Site for each individual user and to notify users about updates to the Site or promotional offers or opportunities that we believe will be of interest to you. OUR WEBSITE(S) share aggregated information with third parties for both advertising and promotional purposes. 

OUR WEBSITE(S) do not share your personal information with third parties without your permission. 

**How to Unsubscribe from Newsletters** If you'd rather not receive news and updates via e-mail, simply: Send a blank email to [remove-galveston@sonic.sparklist.com](mailto:remove-galveston@sonic.sparklist.com) and write "unsubscribe" in the subject line, or Send a letter to Customer Service, Galveston.com & Company, Inc, 523 24th Street, Galveston, TX 77550. **Children and Privacy** OUR WEBSITE(S) encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online, and to be fully familiar with the sites visited by their children. No information should be submitted to or posted on the Site by users under the age of 13 without the consent of their parent or guardian. Personal information from anyone registering on the site and reporting they are under the age of 13 is not kept in our database. **Links to Other Sites** It is important to note that OUR WEBSITE(S) contain links to sites other than OUR WEBSITE(S), and that those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as OUR WEBSITE(S). For instance, if you click on an advertisement on OUR WEBSITE(S) and to an entirely different site. This can include links from advertisers, content providers and partners who may use OUR WEBSITE(S)'s logo and or style as a result of a co-branding agreement. These sites may send their own cookies to you, and may collect data and make uses of it that OUR WEBSITE(S) would not.

OUR WEBSITE(S) reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a revised privacy policy. You can e-mail us with any further questions at [privacy@galveston.com](mailto:privacy@galveston.com).
